[
  {
    "question": "If you eat 33 chocolates every day for 20 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "665",
      "660",
      "655",
      "670"
    ],
    "answer": "660"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 5 chocolates every day for 15 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "70",
      "80",
      "85",
      "75"
    ],
    "answer": "75"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 47 chocolates every day for 18 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "851",
      "856",
      "841",
      "846"
    ],
    "answer": "846"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 46 chocolates every day for 47 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "2157",
      "2162",
      "2172",
      "2167"
    ],
    "answer": "2162"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 37 chocolates every day for 33 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1231",
      "1216",
      "1221",
      "1226"
    ],
    "answer": "1221"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 48 chocolates every day for 4 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "192",
      "202",
      "187",
      "197"
    ],
    "answer": "192"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 44 chocolates every day for 23 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1012",
      "1022",
      "1007",
      "1017"
    ],
    "answer": "1012"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 22 chocolates every day for 17 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "384",
      "369",
      "374",
      "379"
    ],
    "answer": "374"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 23 chocolates every day for 29 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "667",
      "677",
      "672",
      "662"
    ],
    "answer": "667"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 30 chocolates every day for 48 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1450",
      "1435",
      "1440",
      "1445"
    ],
    "answer": "1440"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 24 chocolates every day for 40 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "960",
      "970",
      "955",
      "965"
    ],
    "answer": "960"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 34 chocolates every day for 49 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1671",
      "1676",
      "1661",
      "1666"
    ],
    "answer": "1666"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 35 chocolates every day for 11 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "380",
      "390",
      "395",
      "385"
    ],
    "answer": "385"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 31 chocolates every day for 7 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "222",
      "217",
      "227",
      "212"
    ],
    "answer": "217"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 32 chocolates every day for 50 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1595",
      "1610",
      "1605",
      "1600"
    ],
    "answer": "1600"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 10 chocolates every day for 9 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "100",
      "90",
      "85",
      "95"
    ],
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 11 chocolates every day for 49 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "549",
      "534",
      "539",
      "544"
    ],
    "answer": "539"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 3 chocolates every day for 46 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "138",
      "133",
      "148",
      "143"
    ],
    "answer": "138"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 9 chocolates every day for 15 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "145",
      "130",
      "140",
      "135"
    ],
    "answer": "135"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 46 chocolates every day for 5 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "230",
      "225",
      "235",
      "240"
    ],
    "answer": "230"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 27 chocolates every day for 5 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "145",
      "130",
      "140",
      "135"
    ],
    "answer": "135"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 32 chocolates every day for 17 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "549",
      "554",
      "544",
      "539"
    ],
    "answer": "544"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 36 chocolates every day for 42 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1517",
      "1507",
      "1522",
      "1512"
    ],
    "answer": "1512"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 48 chocolates every day for 21 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1003",
      "1013",
      "1018",
      "1008"
    ],
    "answer": "1008"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 18 chocolates every day for 22 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "401",
      "396",
      "406",
      "391"
    ],
    "answer": "396"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 15 chocolates every day for 50 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "745",
      "750",
      "760",
      "755"
    ],
    "answer": "750"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 33 chocolates every day for 10 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "340",
      "325",
      "335",
      "330"
    ],
    "answer": "330"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 20 chocolates every day for 1 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "15",
      "20",
      "30"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 46 chocolates every day for 14 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "654",
      "649",
      "639",
      "644"
    ],
    "answer": "644"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 18 chocolates every day for 33 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "594",
      "604",
      "599",
      "589"
    ],
    "answer": "594"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 20 chocolates every day for 24 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "485",
      "480",
      "475",
      "490"
    ],
    "answer": "480"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 3 chocolates every day for 36 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "113",
      "118",
      "103",
      "108"
    ],
    "answer": "108"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 6 chocolates every day for 24 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "149",
      "139",
      "154",
      "144"
    ],
    "answer": "144"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 21 chocolates every day for 25 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "520",
      "535",
      "530",
      "525"
    ],
    "answer": "525"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 8 chocolates every day for 8 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "69",
      "59",
      "74",
      "64"
    ],
    "answer": "64"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 1 chocolates every day for 41 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "41",
      "36",
      "46"
    ],
    "answer": "41"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 48 chocolates every day for 28 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1354",
      "1339",
      "1344",
      "1349"
    ],
    "answer": "1344"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 30 chocolates every day for 42 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1255",
      "1260",
      "1265",
      "1270"
    ],
    "answer": "1260"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 43 chocolates every day for 47 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "2031",
      "2026",
      "2021",
      "2016"
    ],
    "answer": "2021"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 7 chocolates every day for 36 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "247",
      "257",
      "262",
      "252"
    ],
    "answer": "252"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 32 chocolates every day for 35 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1125",
      "1115",
      "1120",
      "1130"
    ],
    "answer": "1120"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 14 chocolates every day for 9 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "136",
      "131",
      "121",
      "126"
    ],
    "answer": "126"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 2 chocolates every day for 23 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "56",
      "51",
      "41",
      "46"
    ],
    "answer": "46"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 39 chocolates every day for 38 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1492",
      "1487",
      "1482",
      "1477"
    ],
    "answer": "1482"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 42 chocolates every day for 2 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "79",
      "94",
      "89",
      "84"
    ],
    "answer": "84"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 10 chocolates every day for 46 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "455",
      "460",
      "470",
      "465"
    ],
    "answer": "460"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 11 chocolates every day for 22 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "237",
      "252",
      "247",
      "242"
    ],
    "answer": "242"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 47 chocolates every day for 2 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "89",
      "104",
      "99",
      "94"
    ],
    "answer": "94"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 27 chocolates every day for 2 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "64",
      "54",
      "49",
      "59"
    ],
    "answer": "54"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 9 chocolates every day for 30 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "270",
      "265",
      "275",
      "280"
    ],
    "answer": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 27 chocolates every day for 23 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "616",
      "621",
      "626",
      "631"
    ],
    "answer": "621"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 21 chocolates every day for 16 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "336",
      "346",
      "331",
      "341"
    ],
    "answer": "336"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 4 chocolates every day for 19 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "86",
      "71",
      "76",
      "81"
    ],
    "answer": "76"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 32 chocolates every day for 22 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "714",
      "709",
      "699",
      "704"
    ],
    "answer": "704"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 15 chocolates every day for 33 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "490",
      "500",
      "505",
      "495"
    ],
    "answer": "495"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 17 chocolates every day for 7 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "119",
      "129",
      "124",
      "114"
    ],
    "answer": "119"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 39 chocolates every day for 13 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "507",
      "502",
      "517",
      "512"
    ],
    "answer": "507"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 49 chocolates every day for 24 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1171",
      "1181",
      "1176",
      "1186"
    ],
    "answer": "1176"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 3 chocolates every day for 24 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "82",
      "72",
      "77",
      "67"
    ],
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 48 chocolates every day for 19 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "922",
      "917",
      "907",
      "912"
    ],
    "answer": "912"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 6 chocolates every day for 3 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "28",
      "13",
      "23"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 7 chocolates every day for 13 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "101",
      "96",
      "86",
      "91"
    ],
    "answer": "91"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 38 chocolates every day for 17 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "641",
      "646",
      "651",
      "656"
    ],
    "answer": "646"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 43 chocolates every day for 32 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1381",
      "1371",
      "1376",
      "1386"
    ],
    "answer": "1376"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 20 chocolates every day for 39 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "790",
      "785",
      "775",
      "780"
    ],
    "answer": "780"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 8 chocolates every day for 9 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "77",
      "67",
      "72",
      "82"
    ],
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 46 chocolates every day for 2 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "87",
      "97",
      "102",
      "92"
    ],
    "answer": "92"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 43 chocolates every day for 23 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "984",
      "994",
      "999",
      "989"
    ],
    "answer": "989"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 9 chocolates every day for 43 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "392",
      "387",
      "382",
      "397"
    ],
    "answer": "387"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 33 chocolates every day for 35 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1160",
      "1165",
      "1155",
      "1150"
    ],
    "answer": "1155"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 46 chocolates every day for 7 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "327",
      "317",
      "322",
      "332"
    ],
    "answer": "322"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 31 chocolates every day for 49 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1514",
      "1519",
      "1529",
      "1524"
    ],
    "answer": "1519"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 38 chocolates every day for 38 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1449",
      "1444",
      "1439",
      "1454"
    ],
    "answer": "1444"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 6 chocolates every day for 34 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "204",
      "214",
      "199",
      "209"
    ],
    "answer": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 3 chocolates every day for 39 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "117",
      "122",
      "112",
      "127"
    ],
    "answer": "117"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 38 chocolates every day for 25 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "950",
      "945",
      "955",
      "960"
    ],
    "answer": "950"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 37 chocolates every day for 16 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "592",
      "587",
      "597",
      "602"
    ],
    "answer": "592"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 49 chocolates every day for 14 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "681",
      "691",
      "686",
      "696"
    ],
    "answer": "686"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 22 chocolates every day for 24 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "523",
      "538",
      "528",
      "533"
    ],
    "answer": "528"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 27 chocolates every day for 18 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "491",
      "496",
      "486",
      "481"
    ],
    "answer": "486"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 41 chocolates every day for 41 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1681",
      "1676",
      "1691",
      "1686"
    ],
    "answer": "1681"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 6 chocolates every day for 23 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "138",
      "133",
      "143",
      "148"
    ],
    "answer": "138"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 33 chocolates every day for 44 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1447",
      "1452",
      "1457",
      "1462"
    ],
    "answer": "1452"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 20 chocolates every day for 14 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "285",
      "290",
      "280",
      "275"
    ],
    "answer": "280"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 34 chocolates every day for 38 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1292",
      "1297",
      "1302",
      "1287"
    ],
    "answer": "1292"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 18 chocolates every day for 32 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "586",
      "581",
      "576",
      "571"
    ],
    "answer": "576"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 34 chocolates every day for 40 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1365",
      "1360",
      "1370",
      "1355"
    ],
    "answer": "1360"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 29 chocolates every day for 24 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "696",
      "706",
      "701",
      "691"
    ],
    "answer": "696"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 42 chocolates every day for 40 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1680",
      "1675",
      "1685",
      "1690"
    ],
    "answer": "1680"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 9 chocolates every day for 49 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "436",
      "446",
      "451",
      "441"
    ],
    "answer": "441"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 4 chocolates every day for 14 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "61",
      "66",
      "56",
      "51"
    ],
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 29 chocolates every day for 47 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1363",
      "1368",
      "1373",
      "1358"
    ],
    "answer": "1363"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 42 chocolates every day for 6 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "247",
      "257",
      "252",
      "262"
    ],
    "answer": "252"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 5 chocolates every day for 1 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "10",
      "5",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 26 chocolates every day for 6 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "166",
      "161",
      "156",
      "151"
    ],
    "answer": "156"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 37 chocolates every day for 10 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "365",
      "380",
      "375",
      "370"
    ],
    "answer": "370"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 28 chocolates every day for 5 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "150",
      "145",
      "135",
      "140"
    ],
    "answer": "140"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 36 chocolates every day for 50 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1810",
      "1805",
      "1795",
      "1800"
    ],
    "answer": "1800"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 36 chocolates every day for 37 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1337",
      "1327",
      "1332",
      "1342"
    ],
    "answer": "1332"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 42 chocolates every day for 5 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "215",
      "210",
      "220",
      "205"
    ],
    "answer": "210"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 27 chocolates every day for 43 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1166",
      "1161",
      "1171",
      "1156"
    ],
    "answer": "1161"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 43 chocolates every day for 6 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "268",
      "253",
      "263",
      "258"
    ],
    "answer": "258"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 17 chocolates every day for 26 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "442",
      "452",
      "437",
      "447"
    ],
    "answer": "442"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 6 chocolates every day for 21 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "136",
      "131",
      "121",
      "126"
    ],
    "answer": "126"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 19 chocolates every day for 10 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "190",
      "185",
      "195",
      "200"
    ],
    "answer": "190"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 31 chocolates every day for 47 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1452",
      "1457",
      "1462",
      "1467"
    ],
    "answer": "1457"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 34 chocolates every day for 15 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "505",
      "515",
      "520",
      "510"
    ],
    "answer": "510"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 39 chocolates every day for 5 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "205",
      "195",
      "190",
      "200"
    ],
    "answer": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 42 chocolates every day for 43 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1806",
      "1811",
      "1801",
      "1816"
    ],
    "answer": "1806"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 28 chocolates every day for 48 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1349",
      "1344",
      "1339",
      "1354"
    ],
    "answer": "1344"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 36 chocolates every day for 39 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1404",
      "1399",
      "1409",
      "1414"
    ],
    "answer": "1404"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 13 chocolates every day for 40 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "525",
      "530",
      "520",
      "515"
    ],
    "answer": "520"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 42 chocolates every day for 2 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "84",
      "89",
      "94",
      "79"
    ],
    "answer": "84"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 48 chocolates every day for 20 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "955",
      "970",
      "965",
      "960"
    ],
    "answer": "960"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 11 chocolates every day for 37 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "402",
      "417",
      "407",
      "412"
    ],
    "answer": "407"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 4 chocolates every day for 26 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "99",
      "104",
      "114",
      "109"
    ],
    "answer": "104"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 20 chocolates every day for 31 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "630",
      "625",
      "615",
      "620"
    ],
    "answer": "620"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 47 chocolates every day for 27 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1274",
      "1279",
      "1264",
      "1269"
    ],
    "answer": "1269"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 20 chocolates every day for 28 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "570",
      "555",
      "565",
      "560"
    ],
    "answer": "560"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 41 chocolates every day for 44 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1804",
      "1809",
      "1799",
      "1814"
    ],
    "answer": "1804"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 1 chocolates every day for 19 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "24",
      "14",
      "29"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 49 chocolates every day for 7 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "353",
      "338",
      "348",
      "343"
    ],
    "answer": "343"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 12 chocolates every day for 20 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "240",
      "245",
      "250",
      "235"
    ],
    "answer": "240"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 23 chocolates every day for 47 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1091",
      "1086",
      "1081",
      "1076"
    ],
    "answer": "1081"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 35 chocolates every day for 42 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1475",
      "1470",
      "1480",
      "1465"
    ],
    "answer": "1470"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 1 chocolates every day for 4 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "9",
      "14",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 3 chocolates every day for 47 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "151",
      "141",
      "136",
      "146"
    ],
    "answer": "141"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 12 chocolates every day for 13 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "156",
      "166",
      "151",
      "161"
    ],
    "answer": "156"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 17 chocolates every day for 3 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "61",
      "51",
      "56"
    ],
    "answer": "51"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 33 chocolates every day for 47 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1551",
      "1561",
      "1546",
      "1556"
    ],
    "answer": "1551"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 27 chocolates every day for 37 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1009",
      "994",
      "999",
      "1004"
    ],
    "answer": "999"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 31 chocolates every day for 26 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "816",
      "806",
      "801",
      "811"
    ],
    "answer": "806"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 38 chocolates every day for 22 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "846",
      "836",
      "841",
      "831"
    ],
    "answer": "836"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 29 chocolates every day for 41 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1184",
      "1189",
      "1194",
      "1199"
    ],
    "answer": "1189"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 9 chocolates every day for 17 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "163",
      "158",
      "153",
      "148"
    ],
    "answer": "153"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 38 chocolates every day for 26 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "983",
      "993",
      "998",
      "988"
    ],
    "answer": "988"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 33 chocolates every day for 49 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1617",
      "1627",
      "1622",
      "1612"
    ],
    "answer": "1617"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 4 chocolates every day for 50 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "210",
      "195",
      "200",
      "205"
    ],
    "answer": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 15 chocolates every day for 42 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "640",
      "630",
      "625",
      "635"
    ],
    "answer": "630"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 23 chocolates every day for 38 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "869",
      "874",
      "879",
      "884"
    ],
    "answer": "874"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 3 chocolates every day for 30 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "100",
      "90",
      "85",
      "95"
    ],
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 8 chocolates every day for 31 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "253",
      "248",
      "258",
      "243"
    ],
    "answer": "248"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 20 chocolates every day for 9 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "185",
      "180",
      "175",
      "190"
    ],
    "answer": "180"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 29 chocolates every day for 25 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "725",
      "735",
      "720",
      "730"
    ],
    "answer": "725"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 31 chocolates every day for 28 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "873",
      "878",
      "863",
      "868"
    ],
    "answer": "868"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 43 chocolates every day for 8 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "354",
      "339",
      "344",
      "349"
    ],
    "answer": "344"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 19 chocolates every day for 39 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "751",
      "736",
      "746",
      "741"
    ],
    "answer": "741"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 10 chocolates every day for 11 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "110",
      "120",
      "115",
      "105"
    ],
    "answer": "110"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 2 chocolates every day for 42 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "89",
      "79",
      "84",
      "94"
    ],
    "answer": "84"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 18 chocolates every day for 16 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "293",
      "283",
      "298",
      "288"
    ],
    "answer": "288"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 33 chocolates every day for 45 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "1480",
      "1485",
      "1495",
      "1490"
    ],
    "answer": "1485"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 33 chocolates every day for 21 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "703",
      "693",
      "698",
      "688"
    ],
    "answer": "693"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 8 chocolates every day for 34 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "267",
      "277",
      "272",
      "282"
    ],
    "answer": "272"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 25 chocolates every day for 32 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "805",
      "795",
      "800",
      "810"
    ],
    "answer": "800"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 13 chocolates every day for 8 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "114",
      "99",
      "104",
      "109"
    ],
    "answer": "104"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 32 chocolates every day for 17 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "539",
      "554",
      "549",
      "544"
    ],
    "answer": "544"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 32 chocolates every day for 27 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "864",
      "874",
      "859",
      "869"
    ],
    "answer": "864"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 22 chocolates every day for 31 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "692",
      "677",
      "687",
      "682"
    ],
    "answer": "682"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 23 chocolates every day for 19 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "437",
      "447",
      "432",
      "442"
    ],
    "answer": "437"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you eat 5 chocolates every day for 21 days, how many chocolates will you eat? (Don't lie!)",
    "options": [
      "100",
      "105",
      "115",
      "110"
    ],
    "answer": "105"
  }
]